UNITE Photographs 6000/044 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Photographs
1920-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/044 P
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Photographs.
7564848
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 31, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of over twenty-five hundred photographs and over one hundred slides and several audio CD's. Pictures showing the history of UNITE, ACTWU, Labor Leaders, strikes, protests, boycotts, immigration and various types of labor actions.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/012 P: UNITE Northeast Department Photographs 6000/016 P: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs 6000/018 P: UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council Photographs 6000/020 P: UNITE Research Department Photographs 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/033 P: UNITE Local 155 Photographs 6000/037 P: UNITE Communications Department Photographs 6000/043 P: UNITE Editor Photographs 6000/049 P: UNITE Local 9 Photographs 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Organizaiton--Photographs; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees--Photographs; UNITE HERE (Organization)--Photographs
7564848
- ACTWU History - Immigration, families, children (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  10 photographs
- ACTWU History - Labor Leaders (Box 1, Folder 2)
  11 photographs
- ACWTU History - Shop Scenes - Homework - Workers (Box 1, Folder 3)
  27 photographs; 1 news paper clipping; 1 negative
- ACTWU History - Strikes, Tultex, JP Stevens - Labor actions (Box 1, Folder 4)
  35 photographs; negatives
- ACTWU Southern Region March (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Art/Photography (Box 1, Folder 6)
  18 photographs
- Buffalo (Dotter) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  14 photographs
- Child Labor (Ernesto Mora, NYC 1990) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  15 photographs
- Civil Rights (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Civil Rights Demonstrations (Box 1, Folder 10)
  7 photographs; negatives
- Cone Mills (Box 1, Folder 11)
  34 photographs; contact sheets
- Demonstrations, Leafleting, Group Portrait (ACTWU) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  9 photographs
- Dotter, Earl Photographer (Box 1, Folder 13)
  19 photographs; contact sheets; calendar
- Dotter, Earl (Box 1, Folder 14)
  30 photographs; contact sheets
- Empire (Box 1, Folder 15)
  12 photographs
- Farah Boycott (Box 1, Folder 16)
  96 photographs; negatives
- Farah Boycott (Box 1, Folder 17)
  75 photographs
- Gastonia Strike 1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Haiti (Box 2, Folder 2)
  16 photographs; negatives; contact sheets
- Louis Harrill - Cotton Dust (Box 2, Folder 3)
  2 photographs
- Hats - Millinery (Box 2, Folder 4)
  5 photographs
- Hats - Arlington Hat Company (NYC) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  1 photograph
- Health and Safety (Dotter) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  40 pages
- Henderson, NC (Box 2, Folder 7)
- illman, Bessie and Philoine Fried (Box 2, Folder 8)
  11 photographs; negatives
- Hillman, Sidney (Box 2, Folder 9)
  32 photographs; negatives
- Historical - ACTWU Protests (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Historical - ACWA/TWUA (Box 2, Folder 11)
  7 photographs; 2 news print photographs
- Historical - Amalgamated Bank (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Historical - Capmakers, Millenerers (Box 2, Folder 13)
  30 photographs
- Historical - Children (Box 2, Folder 14)
  28 photographs
- Historical - Children (Box 2, Folder 15)
  47 photographs
- Historical - Child Labor (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Historical - Clothing (Box 2, Folder 17)
  4 photographs
- Historical - Commissaries (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Historical - Fall River (Box 2, Folder 19)
  30 photo copies of photographs
- Historical - Immigration (Box 2, Folder 20)
  36 photographs; contact sheets
- Historical - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 21)
  14 photographs; negative
- Historical - Laundry Workers (ACWA) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  17 photographs
- Historical - Organizing Drives (Box 2, Folder 23)
  3 photographs
- Historical - Shops and Homework (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Historical - Street Scenes (Box 3, Folder 2)
  37 photographs
- Historical - Street Scenes (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Historical - Textile Workers (Box 3, Folder 4)
  9 photographs; negative
- Historical - Tragedies, riots (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Historical - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Historical - Women Workers (Box 3, Folder 7)
  22 photographs
- Historical - Workers (Box 3, Folder 8)
  8 photographs
- Historical Workers by Lewis Hine (Box 3, Folder 9)
  24 photographs
- Historical - Uprising of 1934 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- J/P. Stevens - Allendale Election, Nov. 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens - Japan (Box 3, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens - Tower (Box 3, Folder 14)
  29 photographs
- J.P. Stevens - General (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Labor Unity - Dyers Locals, N.J. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  42 photographs
- Labor Unity - "Faces," ACTWU Cooking Series (Box 3, Folder 17)
  36 photographs
- Labor Unity - Guild guitars (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Labor unity - Hat Plant Feature Story (3/1985) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  1 photograph; 1 news article
- Labor Unity - Health and Safety (Box 3, Folder 20)
  16 photographs; negative; contact sheets
- Labor Unity - How Textiles are Made (Box 3, Folder 21)
  69 photographs
- Labor Unity - How Textiles are made (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Labor Unity - Local 1758, Adjusto Chair Company - ergonomics (Box 4, Folder 1)
  7 photographs
- Labor Unity - Local 2326, Garden State Tannery (Box 4, Folder 2)
  8 photographs; negative; contact sheet
- Labor Unity - Plant and Mill Closings (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Labor Unity - Stetson Hat Tour (5/1986) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Labor Unity - Working Mothers (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Leafletting (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 7)
  49 photographs; negatives
- Miscellaneous - Canada (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous - Music and Dance (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous - Social Events (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous - Theater (Box 4, Folder 11)
  6 photographs
- National Health Care - 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Text
- Publications - Health and Safety (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Partners in Prevention; Stop the Pain! (booklets)
- Publications - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Shop Talk; Threads of History; First Annual International Labor Rights Awards Dinner (1991)
- Publication Logos (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Sewing (Gumpert) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  32 photographs
- Shoes (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Sol Stetin (Box 4, Folder 18)
  44 photographs; Photos of Sol Stetin, VI-2004 - moved to CD/DVD cabinet ---- 415--44--CD--2--D
- Suzy Curtains (Box 4, Folder 19)
  10 photographs; negatives; contact sheets
- Synthetics (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Textile Workers (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Threads (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Tultex (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Voter Registration (Box 5, Folder 1)
  15 photographs; contact sheets
- Voter Registration - 1992 Phone Banks (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Weaving (Box 5, Folder 3)
  33 photographs; negative
- Weaving (Box 5, Folder 4)
  25 photographs; 1 news paper photograph
- Women's suffrage (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Workers - Atlanta, GA; 1993 or 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  55 photographs
- Working - Laundry (Box 5, Folder 7)
  3 photographs; contact sheet
- Working - Tailor and Clothing (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Working Men (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Working Women (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Working Women (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Worth Textiles (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Photocopy (Box 5, Folder 13)
  27 photographs; negatives
- Xerox (Box 5, Folder 14)
  38 photographs; negative
- Yarn (Box 5, Folder 15)
  33 photographs; news paper clippings
- #6 Hordis Committee (Box 5, Folder 16)
  negatives
- ACTWU Convention - June 15-19, 1987 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 5, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Import Press Conference - August 1985 (Negs) (Box 5, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Southern Regional Textile Joint Board Conference, Atlanta - 4/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 5, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Southern Textile Region Joint Board Meeting, Atlanta, GA -- 4/1989 (Negs) (Box 5, Folder 20)
- ACTWU Summer School, Dahlonega - 8/1988 (Negs and Contact Prints) (Box 5, Folder 21)
- AH Labor Council - Stewart ACUFF - March 13, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Negatives
- Allied - Knoxville, TN; Plusmark - Greenville, TN -- October 1987 (Negs) (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Armitage Shanks - England - August 1986 (Negs & Contact Sheets) (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Armitage Shank - Kilgore, TX - Sept. 11, 1986 (negs & Contact Prints) (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bates Nightwear Workers (Diane Dunlap) - 9/1988 (Negs) (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Batesville Casket Campaign - Nashua, NH March 26, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Benay - Albee Workers, NY and VA - 7/1988 (Negs) (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Bi-County Joint Board and Shop Stewards - May 1986 (Negs and Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Buster Brown - Chattanooga, TN - August 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- J.B. Comen - Celanese (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Cannon Mills 1985 Election (Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cannon Mills and Phillip Morris Workers - June to August 1985 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Cannon Mills Workers - August 1983 (Contact Prints and Negs) (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cannon Settlement - January 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Cannon Workers, Carbon Fibers Workers - Rock Hill, SC - June 1985 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Democratic national Convention - 7/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Diversco Trucks & Cannon Property - Kanapolis, NC - March 1985 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Dobbs First Contract Ratification, Charlotte, NC -- 7/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Dobbs Workers - Charlotte, NC - 12/1988 (Negatives) (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Dobbs Workers, Charlotte, NC -- 7/1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Editors' Conference, Charlotte, NC and Tam Ceramics Steelworkers, Buffalo, NY -- 11-12/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- EEOC Applicants - J.P. Stevens - Laurinburg, NC -- December 1986 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 15)
- EEOC Filing on Lichtenberg w/Cong. John Lewis, Atlanta, GA -- 12/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Empire Distribution Election Night, Atlanta, GA -- 2/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Empire or Bondo Workers, Atlanta, GA -- Spring 1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Fielderesh Members - Local 1703, Fieldale, VA - 6/1989 (Negatives) (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Findlay Industries, Ohio -- 3/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Fleischman, Broadmax, Smith, & Thames, Columbus, GA -- 11/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Furtex -- November 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Gardner Manufacturing Workers -- 3/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Gardner Manufacturing OH -- 3/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Gardner manufacturing TN -- 3-4/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 25)
- HBJ Leafletting - Orlando, FL -- March 13, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Hines, Bagwell, Walls, Honeycutt -- 1985 (Negatives) (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Earl Hunnicutt -- ACTWU Staff -- Winter 1986 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Import Demonstration - Greensboro, NC -- 6/1986 (Negatives & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens Election Night -- 12/1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens Leafletting, Drakes Branch, VA -- 12/1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens Workers - Roanoke Rapids, NC -- October 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens Workers, Roanoke Rapids, NC -- 11/1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens Workers -- Drakes Branch, VA -- November 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Jesse Jackson Labor Reception - ACTWU DNC Delegates, Atlanta, GA -- 7/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Jesse Jackson at Standard Products, NC -- 2/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Jobs with Justice -- 4/1988 (Negatives) (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Candlelight Vigil Honoring martin Luther King -- 1/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  King, Martin Luther, Jr.
- Martin Luther King Day Celebration -- Louisville and Keysville, GA -- 1/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 39)
- King, March -- Atlanta, GA -- November 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Martin Luther, Jr.
- King, Martin L. Jr. March, Atlanta, GA -- 1/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Labor Day March -- Atlanta, GA -- September 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Labor Day March, Columbus, GA -- 9/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Labor for Justice Reception, Atlanta, GA -- 7/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Jacob Lewis, Columbus, GA -- 10/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Lichtenberg Campaign -- 7/1988 (Negatives) (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Lichtenberg Shop Steward Class, Augusta, GA -- 6/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Lichtenberg Workers -- Waynesboro & Louisville, GA -- 2-4/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Local 1093 - Celanese Rock Hill S. Carolina - March 1986 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Magia - August 1986 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Miami Bi-County All-American Rally --- 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Other Union Members, Martinsville, VA -- 7/1989 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Reagan, Ronald -- Greensboro, NC -- June 1986 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Reeves - 3/1987 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Reeves Contract Ratification (Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Reeves Election - April 1986 (Negs and Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Reeves Shipping Department -- March 1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Reeves Workers and Negotiations -- March & April 1986 (Negs & Contact prints) (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Regional Joint Board Meeting -- April 18-19, 1986 Negs & Contact prints) (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Angie Rogers, Trend Mills Workers, Rome, GA -- 9/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Jina Russell -- Local 1781 -- May 1986 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- SCLC March for Justice and Regional Conference - 4/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 62)
- SCLC Pilgrimage for Economic Justice, GA -- 4/1988 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Schoeller Workers, Sumter, SC -- 8/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Carol Sheerer - Staff Press Conference - Cannon -- 1985 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Sheinkman, et. al. at Cannon. 1985 (Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Sots of Atlanta, GA -- August 1987 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Spinnerin (Schoeller) Varns. Hackensack, NJ -- 8/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Standard Products Workers. Rocky Mount, NC -- 3/1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Stimson, Corliss and Andrea - Reeves - April 1987 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Taxi Drivers - Kola Kowagne & Pork Chop - January 1988 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Taxi Drivers, Atlanta Airport -- 9-10/1987 (Negs) (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Taxi Drivers of Atlanta -- Organizing Committee -- June 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  negatives and contact sheets
- Taxi Drivers in Union Office - "Connie and Laverne" -- 3/1988 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Taxi Drivers' School and Promoting at World Congress Center, Atlanta, GA -- 1987 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Taxis at World Congress Center -- 3/1988 (Negatives), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Tennessee Woolen Mills -- July 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Tultex -- 1994 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Tultex Workers, Martinsville, VA -- 6 to 8 /1989 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Underwood & Armstrong - Cannon -- march 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Unidentified -- Tennessee -- 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Unidentified negatives (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Unidentified Negatives (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Unidentified Contact Prints (Box 7, Folder 12)
- United Taxi Drivers after injunction hearing - Atlanta, GA -- July 28, 1987 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 13)
- United Taxi Drivers of Atlanta and MLK Day March -- 1/1988 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Volunteer Organizers, Tenneford Weaving -- 10/1987 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Wellman and Woodside -- Headshots (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Welsh Workers - Gordonsville, TN -- July 1987 (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Welsh Workers -- Union Springs, AL -- July 1987 (Negs) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Wilen Election Day (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Wilen Election Victory -- 4/1994 (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Photocopy -- California -- Chuck Shephard (Negs & Contact Prints) (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 22)
  23 photographs; news paper photographs; negatives
- Historical -- 1920s, 1920-1930 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  10 photographs; negatives
- Historical - 1930s, 1930-1940 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  31 photographs; negatives
- Historical - 1933 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  9 photographs; negatives
- Historical -- 1937; Dallas, TX (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Historical 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Historical -- 1958 Dress Strike (Box 7, Folder 28)
  13 photographs; negatives
- Historical -- Kellwood Strike, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  21 photographs; news paper articles; negatives
- Historical - Powell Hearings, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Crisis (Nov. 1962); David Dubinsky: Why his throne is wobbling; The Truth about the ILGWU; Testimony of Herbert Hill; Correspondence from David Dubinsky; Correspondence from Emanuel Muravchik (Jewish Labor Committee); JUSTICE - Sept. 1, 1962 issue
- ILGWU - 75th Anniversary (Box 7, Folder 31)
  8 photographs; news paper article
- IGWU History - Early 1900's - Labor Actions (Box 8, Folder 1)
  47 photographs; negatives
- ILGWU History -- Homework, Child Labor, Families, Immigration, Children (Box 8, Folder 2)
  22 photographs; negatives
- ILGWU History -- Misc. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- ILGWU History - Rallies (Box 8, Folder 4)
  6 photographs; negatives
- ILGWU History - Negatives (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Members - Portraits (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ILGWU History - Gus Tyler's "Look for the Union Label" (Box 8, Folder 7)
- King, Martin Luther, Jr. with David Dubinsky (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Local 155 - Knit goods Workers Union (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Our First Fifty Years
- March on Washington - for jobs and freedom - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Shop Scenes - 1900-Present (Box 8, Folder 11)
  8 photographs; negative
- Shop Scenes (Bob Gumpert) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  20 photographs; contact sheets
- Solidarity (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Work-Related Disasters (Triangle) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  9 photo copies of photographs
- Brooks Brothers Organizing (Schoichet) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  11 slides
- Chipman Lane (B-L) (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Civil rights (Box 8, Folder 17)
- COPE #27 Negatives (Dave Sanders) (Box 8, Folder 18)
- GAP Sweatshop Ad. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  CD moved to CD/DVD cabinet -- box 12 -- 415--44--cd--2--d
- King, Coretta Scott (Box 8, Folder 20)
- King Day, Greensboro, NC (Dave Sanders) -- 1/15/2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  70 photographs
- King Day, Greensboro, NC (Dave Sanders) Negatives (Box 9, Folder 1)
- K-Mart Boycott-Southern Region Locals -- 4/8/1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- K-Mart Boycott (Bruce Raynor) -- 8 April 1998 (slides) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  15 slides
- Levi's - Blue Ridge (Lane B-L) (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Lobby Day (Dave Sanders) -- 2/4/2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Lobby Day (Dave Sanders) -- 2/15/2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  23 photographs
- Lobby Day (Dave Sanders)-- Negatives -- 2/4 - 2/5/2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NYC Laundries (Gary Schoichet) -- 12/16/2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  96 photographs
- Peerless (Lane B-L) (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Pilon - Organizing (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Roadmaster (Lane B-L) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Shops-Laundry (di Nuzzo) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Shops-Laundry (Schoichet) slides and prints (Box 9, Folder 14)
  3 photographs; 5 slides
- Southern Regional Union Demonstrations (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 15)
- T.J. Maxx Rally, Local 289 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- T.J. Maxx Rally, Local 399 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- T.J. Maxx/Marshall's Local 4 Rally (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Triangle Ceremony - 3/25/2004 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  CD moved to CD/DVD cabinet -- 415--44--CD--2--D
- UNITE Merger Convention - Contact Prints (1) (Box 9, Folder 20)
- UNITE Merger Convention - Contact Prints (2) (Box 9, Folder 21)
- unite Merger Convention - Contact Prints (3) (Box 9, Folder 22)
- UNITE Convention 2003 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  empty
- UNITE Convention 2003 -- Digital Files (Box 9, Folder 24)
  Zip Drive; CDs moved to CD/DVD cabinet --- 415--44--CD--2--D ---- Jack Morton - UNITE! Convention 2003 Final PowerPoints 7/21/03-7/24/03; UNITE convention 2003 photos [not PC compatible]; Jack Morton - UNITE 2003 Convention Images
- "With these Hands" -- Crafts Feature -- 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  44 photographs
- Digital images -- CFF video stills (Box 9, Folder 26)
  1 zip drive
- Anti-Sweatshop March (Hollenshead) - NYC 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  MUST CONTACT PHOTOGRAPHER --- 2 oversize photographs
- Diversity - 1990 Holiday Cover (Box 10, Folder 2)
  2 oversize photographs
- Guild Guitars (Schoichet) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  1 oversize photograph
- Laundry Worker (Schoichet) (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Shop and Laundry Workers (Gumpert) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  2 oversize photograph
- Levi's San Benito, Tx (Cara Metz) - Alice Torres (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Liz Claiborne Warehouse, Local 99 (Hollenshead) -- 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Mother Jones (Box 10, Folder 8)
- UNITE Members (Box 10, Folder 9)
  1 photograph; contact sheets
- Voice @ Work March (Bruce Raynor) - NYC (Contact Prints) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Schoichet - ASAI - 11/20/2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  34 slides
- Garry Schoichet -- Immigration/Citizenship - Las Vegas -- 2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  38 slides
- Garry Schoichet - UNITE Winter 2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  32 slides
- Negatives - loose in box (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Sol Stein -- VI-2004 (Box 11)
  - Photographs of Sol Stetin (CD) -- VI-2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- GAP Sweatshop Ad (Box 12)
  - GAP Ad (CD) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Triangle Ceremony - 3/25/2004 (Box 13)
  - Triangle Ceremony 3/25/2004 (CD) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- UNITE! Convention 2003 -- Final PowerPoints 7/21/03-7/24/03 (Box 14)
  - UNITE! Convention 2003 - Final PowerPoints -- 7/21/2004-7/25/2004 (CD) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- UNITE Convention 2003 Photos (not PC Compatibile) (Box 15)
  - UNITE Convention 2003 Photographs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- UNITE 2003 Convention Images (Box 16)
  - UNITE 2003 Convention Images (CD) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Box 1 OP -- Oversize Photographs, 1953-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  1- St. Jean, 6ieme Conference 7.9. Novembre 1953 - Bureau & Conjoint de Montreal [Montreal Joint Board ACWA - 6th conference - Nov. 7-8, 1953, St. Johns Que]; 1-Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC - Special Convention - June 1-4, 1976 --- 2 photographs